https://www.netadmintools.com/privacy-policy/

Menu
×MainHomeNetwork Monitoring SoftwareApplication Monitoring SoftwareBandwidth Monitoring SoftwareSyslog ServersTFTP ServersEvent Log Analysis SoftwareHelp Desk SoftwareIPAM SoftwareNetflow Analyzers and CollectorsNetwork Configuration Management SoftwareVN Manager & Monitoring SoftwareWake On Lan ToolsInfo & ContactContactTerms of UsePrivacy PolicyDisclaimerLegal© 2016 NetAdminTools.comAll Rights ReservedHomeMonitoringBackup/RecoveryGNU/LinuxAdministrationPerlRubyDatabaseProtecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the https://www.NetAdminTools.com and NetAdminTools.com and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to NetAdminTools.com include https://www.NetAdminTools and NetAdminTools. The NetAdminTools website is a News, Information, Reviews, Tutorials, Guides site. By using the NetAdminTools website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal Information We do not collect personally identifiable information from our users. We may gather personal or non-personal information in the future.Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by NetAdminTools. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the NetAdminTools website.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through NetAdminTools’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.NetAdminTools encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from NetAdminTools so that you can understand how those websites collect use and share your information. NetAdminTools is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the NetAdminTools website.Use of Cookies The NetAdminTools website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purpose of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize NetAdminTools pages, or register with NetAdminTools site or services, a cookie helps NetAdminTools to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same NetAdminTools website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the NetAdminTools features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the NetAdminTools services or websites you visit.Security of your Personal InformationNetAdminTools secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.Children Under Thirteen NetAdminTools does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen if you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.Opt-Out & Unsubscribe We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from NetAdminTools by contacting us here: – Email: contact (@) netadmintools.comChanges to this Statement NetAdminTools will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. NetAdminTools encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how NetAdminTools is protecting your information.Contact Information NetAdminTools welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that NetAdminTools has not adhered to this Statement, Please contact NetAdminTools at:NetAdminTools.com 715 NW Hoyt St. #3383A Portland, Oregon 97208Email Address: Contact@netadmintools.comEffective as of October 12, 2016SearchMust Read ResourcesWHITE PAPERNetwork Management Software Buyers GuideWHITE PAPERGNS3 Network Emulator TrainingWHITE PAPERNetflow Best PracticesWHITE PAPERLearn how to Analyze Packet with Deep AnalysisWHITE PAPERHow to Find your Highest Bandwidth UsersInformationContactPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseDisclaimerLegalAboutAbout UsContributeStaff/Authors{"cookieName":"wBounce","isAggressive":false,"isSitewide":true,"hesitation":"2000","openAnimation":false,"exitAnimation":false,"timer":"","sensitivity":"","cookieExpire":"","cookieDomain":"","autoFire":"","isAnalyticsEnabled":false}
